<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Inspired</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">SettingsActivity</string>

    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>

    <!-- Messages Preferences -->
    <string name="signature_title">Your signature</string>
    <string name="reply_title">Default reply action</string>

    <!-- Sync Preferences -->
    <string name="sync_title">Sync email periodically</string>
    <string name="attachment_title">Download incoming attachments</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_on">Automatically download attachments for incoming emails
    </string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_off">Only download attachments when manually requested</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings2">SettingsActivity2</string>
    <string name="autostart_dialog_title">Enable Auto-Start</string>
    <string name="autostart_dialog_message">In order to receive daily Quote notification, please enable Auto-Start. You also can change this setting in app settings. This setting will not affect battery life!</string>
    <string name="autostart_toast_enable">Auto-Start enabled!</string>
    <string name="autostart_toast_disabled">Auto-Start not enabled! Missing feature (NOTIF ON) or aborted by user (NOTIF OFF)</string>
    <string name="autostart_dialog_button">Enable</string>
    <string name="battery_saver_title">Battery Saver</string>
    <string name="battery_saver_message">In order to receive daily Quote notification when battery saver is ON, disable battery saver for this app. You can change this setting in app settings. After dismiss, pop-up for enable run in background should appear, if not, battery saver is already disabled for this app. This setting will not affect battery life!</string>
    <string name="battery_saver_dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="snack_server_problem">Ooops…something is wrong with the remote server!</string>
    <string name="no_fetched_quotes">Ooops......No fetched quotes, please go online and try again!</string>
    <string name="snack_cannot_insert_quote">Cannot insert to favourites, low data storage!</string>
    <string name="chooser_title">Inspired Quote</string>
    <string name="battery_attention">In order to conserve battery life and not to pressure server, notifications will not arrive at exact time that you choose!</string>
    <string name="inserted_favourite">Inserted to favourite</string>
    <string name="error_insert_favourite">Opps…something went wrong!</string>
    <string name="inspire_you">Inspire You</string>
    <string name="no_quotes_cathed">No Quotes Catched!</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">
        <b>Privacy Policy</b>\n
         Ionut Grigore built the Inspired app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by Ionut Grigore at no cost and is intended for use as is.

This pop-up is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.

If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that I collect is used for providing and improving the Service. I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at Inspired unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.
        \n\n<b>Information Collection and Use</b>\n
The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.
        \n\n<b>Log Data</b>\n
        I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in a case of an error in the app I collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing my Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.

        \n\n<b>Children\'s Privacy</b>\n
        These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13.

        \n\n<b>Terms &amp; Conditions</b>\n
        By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the app. You\'re not allowed to copy, or modify the app, any part of the app, or our trademarks in any way. You\'re not allowed to attempt to extract the source code of the app, and you also shouldn\'t try to translate the app into other languages, or make derivative versions. The app itself, and all the trade marks, copyright, database rights and other intellectual property rights related to it, still belong to Ionut Grigore.
        Ionut Grigore is committed to ensuring that the app is as useful and efficient as possible. For that reason, we reserve the right to make changes to the app or to charge for its services, at any time and for any reason. We will never charge you for the app or its services without making it very clear to you exactly what you\'re paying for.
        It\'s your responsibility to keep your phone and access to the app secure. We therefore recommend that you do not jailbreak or root your phone, which is the process of removing software restrictions and limitations imposed by the official operating system of your device. It could make your phone vulnerable to malware/viruses/malicious programs, compromise your phone\'s security features and it could mean that the Inspired app won\'t work properly or at all.
        You should be aware that there are certain things that Ionut Grigore will not take responsibility for. Certain functions of the app will require the app to have an active internet connection. The connection can be Wi-Fi, or provided by your mobile network provider, but Ionut Grigore cannot take responsibility for the app not working at full functionality if you don\'t have access to Wi-Fi, and you don\'t have any of your data allowance left.
        If you\'re using the app outside of an area with Wi-Fi, you should remember that your terms of the agreement with your mobile network provider will still apply. As a result, you may be charged by your mobile provider for the cost of data for the duration of the connection while accessing the app, or other third party charges. In using the app, you\'re accepting responsibility for any such charges, including roaming data charges if you use the app outside of your home territory (i.e. region or country) without turning off data roaming. If you are not the bill payer for the device on which you\'re using the app, please be aware that we assume that you have received permission from the bill payer for using the app.
        Along the same lines, Ionut Grigore cannot always take responsibility for the way you use the app i.e. You need to make sure that your device stays charged – if it runs out of battery and you can\'t turn it on to avail the Service, Ionut Grigore cannot accept responsibility.
        With respect to Ionut Grigore\'s responsibility for your use of the app, when you\'re using the app, it\'s important to bear in mind that although we endeavour to ensure that it is updated and correct at all times, we do rely on third parties to provide information to us so that we can make it available to you. Ionut Grigore accepts no liability for any loss, direct or indirect, you experience as a result of relying wholly on this functionality of the app.
        At some point, we may wish to update the app. The app is currently available on Android – the requirements for system(and for any additional systems we decide to extend the availability of the app to) may change, and you\'ll need to download the updates if you want to keep using the app. Ionut Grigore does not promise that it will always update the app so that it is relevant to you and/or works with the Android version that you have installed on your device. However, you promise to always accept updates to the application when offered to you, We may also wish to stop providing the app, and may terminate use of it at any time without giving notice of termination to you. Unless we tell you otherwise, upon any termination, (a) the rights and licenses granted to you in these terms will end; (b) you must stop using the app, and (if needed) delete it from your device.


        \n\n<b>Changes to This Privacy Policy</b>\n
         I may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

This policy is effective as of 2021-01-09

        \n\n<b>Contact Us</b>\n
        If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, app, do not hesitate to contact me at ionut.grigore@hotmail.com.
    </string>




</resources>